Our packing is done.  Adi, we are going to grandma's place.
Tell your father to behave properly
until we come.
Kept all the stuff.
Which goods?  It is not like he has got a necklace made for us
that we can keep it.  Had asked for a Rakhi.  I have
n't even brought that.
What friend dad, festivals used to come once a year.  Even in that he did
not bring Rakhi for mother.  It
is wrong.  We are bringing it and giving it to you.
They want the gold.   You have
come to the line for gold.  Hey, Rakhi is
tied only with silk.  Why are you
insisting on sleeping?   If you pay
attention then don't give.  If you don't want to bring Rakhi,
refuse clearly.
Ok, good.  One cannot go away angry.
Go halfway through the store.
Come and bring a packet of salty biscuits and keep it in mom's bag.   No. No.  There is
no need to show favour to us by asking for salty biscuits.  No
one remains hungry in our mother's house.  There is no
need to keep half the amount.   Do you
understand?  Hey mom, take it.
Why get so angry?  I don't know whether I will get
something to eat there on time or not, so take this out and
eat it.
Adi, please tell me one thing.  There is no need to keep anything in our bags.
Nor bring any luggage.
Your maternal uncle is capable of
feeding us.
You get so angry that you do
n't understand anything in your anger.  Here
Adi, please go and put this money in mom's bag.
Adimaan is refusing to go, isn't he?
You keep it etc.  He is angry right now.
Hey, I am saying that I don't want anything.  Don't
open ours.  We will not take anything.
Leave
it, Papa
[laughs] it's
Raksha Bandhan.  I thought my brother should take
some stuff for his nephews.